Lee Yun?
Lee Yun!
Lee Yun.
Mom!
Get in, quick!
Lee Yun!
I'm sorry…
I don't know what happened to the mirror.
Mei-ling…
Mei-ling is leaving
with another man.
And An-an.
What?
That's Dr. Sun's car.
They're leaving with him.
I thought you were honest.
To be honest,
you don't decide whether you can go back.
Wei-zhe does.
When he gets to your house,
he'll take down the basement mirror.
When it's time to return,
he'll put it back.
He says that if one mirror is taken down,
none of them will crack.
Dad, it keeps thundering.
How much longer?
A little farther.
To the pavilion.
Lightning.
I saw it,
then turned around and Yoo-shin was gone.
Lightning.
Half an hour ago, you said thunder.
Now you're saying lightning.
Which was it? Can you clarify?
I don't know.
I saw lightning, then Yoo-shin was gone.
He disappeared right before my eyes,
right before my eyes.
I want to know why too.
One last time.
Did you leave Yoo-shin there on purpose?
Dad, the fog's gone. Should we keep going?
Dad,
when Mom's off,
can we all come back together?
On a nice day,
there should be lots of birds, insects,
and the Emperor moth.
My teacher said Emperor moth are gone.
Dad, didn't you know?
I hate the Emperor moth.
They're scary.
Are there a lot over there?
Where?
The world where He Yoo-shin is.
Let's go home. Come on.
I don't want to be He Yoo-shin.
I'm your child, Xu Li-an.
Stop scratching.
You'll get hurt.
- Turn around.
- But it itches.
Here.
Is this better?
Feels good.
Okay. Apply medicine.
Just scratch it a little more.
If you want to go back, go alone.
Why take An-an?
You're just like your wife.
Are you trying to take him away?
Or leave him in the mountains
to get revenge?
I'd never leave him alone
in the mountains.
I couldn't.
Why is the mirror on floor?
He'd better not come back
and take anyone while I'm gone.
What do you mean?
Why did you lie to me?
Why?
Don't be angry.
Wei-zhe knows how much you've done.
He didn't want you to worry,
so he handled everything himself.
That's why he kept it from you.
The mirror cracked,
the passage stayed shut.
He must have done it.
He never wanted An-an and me to go there.
Don't think that way.
Something must have happened,
so he couldn't let you go back.
Honestly,
Wei-zhe really needs you.
You're all he has.
I thought
I could rely on him.
But where was he when I needed him?
Eat up.
I'll bathe you after.
Mei-ling,
I'm begging you.
Don't blame him.
Please.
Mei-ling,
please,
don't blame him.
Where's Jian-cheng?
Where's he?
Can't hear you.
The basement.
Go downstairs and you'll know.
HANG THE MIRROR
BACK IN THE BASEMENT
I HAVE SOMETHING TO SHOW YOU
AND I ALSO HAVE AN-AN'S SUPPLEMENTS.
PSYCHIATRY CLINIC
Take a look.
If it's okay, sign it.
Is she getting divorced too?
It has nothing to do with her.
I can support you monthly
but not indefinitely.
Or I can give you a lump sum.
If you want a job, I know people in Taipei
who can help--
What about the kids?
It's all there. Read it yourself.
We're closed tonight.
Put up the sign when you leave.
Going to Dr. Sun?
Don't.
His wife contacted me.
You plan to leave Xu Wei-zhe,
not go to our world.
Will your choice
affect what he does next?
Is that all you care about?
What else?
Then there's no need to explain.
Mei-ling.
The way he treated his wife,
he'll treat you the same way.
Understand?
- Hello?
- Hello, Dad?
You haven't read my messages or replied.
Mom won't answer either.
I just took her out.
I'm driving. What's wrong?
I want to come home this week.
Don't you have school?
But I wanna come home.
Sure.
Come home if you want.
- I'll pick you up on Friday.
- Really?
Where's Mom? Put her on.
She's cooking.
I'll tell her.
But she only replies by text.
It's been so long since I talked to her.
Is she okay?
She's fine.
I gotta go.
I have to go help her. Bye.
Why do you want Yu-jhen back?
Why not let her come back?
She has to face it eventually.
I'll be a good dad. Don't worry.
Where to?
I'll go make dinner.
Eastern air quality is expected
to reach hazardous AQI levels,
50 times above the safe limit.
Four children with epilepsy
have reportedly died in recent days.
Parents are urged
to keep their children safe.
The government advises children to…
Mom, Dad was great today.
He taught me some hard math
and I learned it right away.
Are you coming home?
Brother!
Da-jun.
You offered, so I came for a drink,
and to check on sister-in-law.
Today isn't a good time.
Da-jun!
Sister-in-law.
Are you cooking?
It smells so good!
Come in.
Have dinner with us.
Brother, I also brought your favorite,
kaoliang liquor.
You didn't have to.
Come on in.
You believe me, right?
Don't drink the soup, remember.
Don't turn it on. It's a waste of power.
Mei-ling said to.
It's humid today.
I know you've had a hard life.
When my mom was sick,
I knew how much she suffered.
I didn't want to lose her.
I wanted her to live for me,
but she had no choice.
You do.
Can you let go of those thoughts?
Remember the Black King Kong at my place?
I said someone gave it to me,
and I'm taking it to Dad in Taipei.
He loves it. Remember?
Of course. How could I forget?
Come on, don't be shy.
The chicken soup is great.
You have to try it.
Get Da-jun a bowl.
No, it's okay.
I'm already full.
You said it smelled good. Have some.
Get Da-jun a bowl.
Okay.
- Have a drink.
- I can do it myself.
Here.
No need. Just a little.
I'm really full.
It's hot.
Try it.
Don't force him if he doesn't want it.
Hey, have you read the contract?
I knew you had a reason for coming.
We're moving out.
I'll get the contract.
Give me the soup.
Sister-in-law, I really don't know
how to help you.
Help me tie him up.
"Tie him up"? How?
First,
the price is firm.
There's no room to negotiate.
Let's do it next month.
We have things to take care of…
and want privacy.
Leave it to me. Don't worry.
Come on, eat. Don't be shy.
Have another drink.
You're going to take
our divorce papers to her.
You want custody?
Do you think you can
take care of them like this?
- I can.
- You can?
How much time do you spend with them?
You don't know how to raise kids
even with my parents' help.
What makes you think you deserve custody?
I'll let you see them anytime.
Isn't that enough?
I'm telling you,
the kids are staying with me.
Take me to court,
the judge will rule in my favor.
Want to try?
Sign it again.
Hello?
Mr. Hsu,
this is Ms. Kao.
I need a witness.
Who are you calling? I have a witness.
Can you help me?
Can you meet me at our usual cafe?
I need your help.
- Give it to me.
- Mr. Hsu.
- Give me the phone!
Hello?
You hit me?
You hit me for that woman?
I don't know what's happened to me.
Maybe I'm just sick of you.
Just sign it.
CALLING SUN RONG-GUANG.
Mei-ling!
Why are you here?
I'm here to take you home.
I don't need your help.
Mei-ling?
- So much blood!
- Sorry, ma'am.
Mrs. Hsu, I have something for you.
What you wanted.
Where's Dr. Sun?
He hit me first.
You heard it, didn't you?
He started it.
- You heard it, right?
- Calm down.
- He started it.
- Relax.
You heard it, right?
Just calm down.
Look, we're divorced.
Are you happy?
Good for you.
He'll never get tired of you.
I'm the only one he's tired of!
Let's go.
Come on.
Come on, hurry.
His original plan
was to take his mother there
that afternoon,
then I'd take An-an there
when the mirror cracked at midnight.
This is your wife's phone.
I saw her photos and messages.
She really loved her kids.
If…
If she knew An-an had epilepsy,
would she still want him?
Lee Yun!
Da-jun is leaving.
- Honey!
- It's fine.
You're drunk.
No way. Only three bottles.
Are you okay?
What did you put in the soup?
She didn't put anything in it.
It's a family matter. Back off.
- Okay.
- I'm fine.
Okay, you're fine.
You're okay.
What's in the soup?
What's wrong?
- I told you, I'm fine.
- Calm down.
- Get it?
- Yeah.
- Stay out of my family business.
- Okay. Fine.
You held my wife's hand?
What…
- What's that?
- Held hands?
- Took my wife home?
- What?
- Bro…
You took my wife home?
Let go!
You took my wife home, right?
Basement.
You've pissed me off.
Trying to kill
your own husband?
Just wait.
I'm sending you to a psych ward.
No! What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Mei-ling,
the mirror cracked.
Mom, why aren't you coming?
I still have things to pack.
When are you coming?
Soon.
Listen to Dad.
Mom will be there very soon.
Be good.
Hsu Wei-zhe told me
An-an's epilepsy would be cured
in your world.
He'll have no health issues,
and he'd grow up safe.
Would you…
Would you take An-an there?
Of course.
Then will you…
Will you take good care of him,
like he's your own child?
Can you promise
to find a way for me
to see An-an and know he's okay?
Okay.
I promise.
An-an.
An-an, come on.
Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
Hurry. Go.
Come on.
An-an, stay here. Wait for me.
Wait for me.
Stay in your room.
Don't open the door for anyone.
Lock the door.
Don't cause trouble.
Mom!
I can't hear you.
What did you say?
Mom!
Hong Mei-ling!
Lee Yun.
Lee Yun,
Jian-cheng.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry…
Did he hurt you?
I'm fine. Are you okay?
Where is he?
Hold on.
Da-jun, are you all right?
Lucky you, huh?
Damn you! All of this is mine!
Jian-cheng!
I'm Jian-cheng.
- Dad.
- An-an.
- Mom.
Why are you here?
You brought him here?
Jian-cheng!
Hey.
Da-jun.
Big Brother.
Who are you?
An-an, come here.
Stay back.
- Don't move.
- Lee Yun, bring An-an over.
- Bring An-an over.
- Calm down.
Just calm down.
An-an, Dad wants you.
Go.
What are you looking at?
I said come here! Do you hear me?
Now!
That's not my dad!
Dad doesn't wear a watch!
He's bad!
Your mom said
you need to go home.
Shut up.
Just shut up.
Mei-ling said
she'd grant her wish.
She'd grant her wish.
Wei-zhe.
Come back.
Please.
Don't do this.
Happy?
I'll take you out every day
once we get there.
You two go. I'm old now.
Just take care of your wife and kids.
Let me go in peace, okay?
I don't want to burden you.
Hsu Li-an,
take care.
Jian-cheng?
Jian-cheng.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Wait.
Don't come over yet.
Jian-cheng!
MISSING PERSON
Do you know what's strangest
about this whole story?
The little boy.
He looks exactly the same
as he did three years ago.
Three years!
He hasn't grown one bit!
Today, Xiao Pan takes us
to the mysterious cave
where he supposedly time-traveled.
You're annoying. Go away.
Don't be like that.
He just wants to be close.
Yeah, right. He just wants my phone.
Sneaky little brat.
I don't.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
An-an,
look what Dad got you.
Thank you, Dad.
Dad put some games on it.
Teach him how to play.
Sis, will you teach me?
You're spoiling him.
He hasn't adjusted. I'm distracting him.
What's on your mind?
What if…
What if we put it back?
I'd do anything for you,
but I can't put
the mirror back.
Mei-ling,
she must really miss An-an.
- And at bedtime, An-an still--
- He'll get used to it.
She'll find a way back if she can.
I can't risk it.
I won't let anyone
or anything
hurt our family again.
Get inside. It's dangerous. Come on.
I'm closing the window.
Keep your head inside.
It's dangerous. Come.
Sit down.
I like visiting Dad in Taipei.
I like Grandpa's house.
Really?
Then don't ask Grandpa
to buy you so many toys every time.
Then I can take you to see him more.
You're playing favorites.
Yoo-shin has many bottles, sketchbooks,
pencils and colored pencils.
He has so much,
and I have nothing.
I'll buy you more water bottles, okay?
No.
I don't want the same stuff.
I need to pee.
Did you wash your hands?
Want some water?
What's wrong? Why so quiet?
Mom?
Will you love me more
if I stop asking for things?
Of course I love you.
I'll always love you.
No matter what.
Buckle up.
We're going to Taipei to see Dad.
Sit tight.
HE YOO-SHIN